Once in a while
a very distant galaxy ...
STAR WARS
Episode 3:
OSVETA SITA
War! Republic breaks ...
under the attacks of the cruel master of Sita,
Count Dukua.
The hero is on both sides.
Evil is everywhere.
A stunning move, wicked
Droid Leader, General Grievus ...
he entered the capital of the Republic
and kidnapped Chancellor Palpatine ...
the leader of the galactic Senate.
While the separatist army droids
trying to escape from the capital ...
with your precious hostage ...
two Jedi are leading the desperate mission
to save the captured chancellor ...
Get him, R2.
Learn, the ship of General Grievous
is in front of us ...
one full of droid-leechers.
I see him.
This will be easy.
Freak, do you hear me?
- I hear, Red Leader.
Mark my position.
Form an escadron behind me.
Behind you,
General Kenobi.
Shine in the position for the attack.
Now the party begins.
Let them pass between us.
Everywhere they are around me.
Get off me ...
- I'm going to help them.
Not. They do their job
that we can do our work.
Projectiles. Come to me.
They missed us.
- They're coming back.
Good, R4. No no.
Do not push it.
Voltage in all generators, R2.
Prepare pushers for reverse.
We hit them, R2.
It's flying for droids.
They hit me. Anakin?
- I see them.
Buzzers.
Watch out, R4. Have...
Oh my God.
They excuse me all the commands.
Move to the left
so that they could be targeted.
Mission.
Go to the main ship.
Find the chancellor.
I'm running out of tricks.
For the name ...
Stop paLjbu. You're not helping me.
- I agree. Bad idea.
I can not see anything.
The cabin was blurred.
There are everywhere, Anakin!
Move to the right.
- Wait. We both will die.
Go.
You can not do anything more.
I'm not going without you, teach me.
Get him down, R2.
Watch it.
R2, hit the buzzer
in the middle eye.
That, you hit him!
- Great, R2.
General's main ship
is in front of us.
Do you notice?
that the shields are still locked?
Sorry, teach me.
I have a bad feeling.
There they are. Get them off.
Find a chancellor, R2.
Chancellor's signal comes from here ...
from the observatory
at the top of this tower.
I feel Count Duku.
I feel the trap.
- The next move?
Activate the trap.
Come back, R2.
You should stay with the ship.
Here is. Take this
and wait for instructions.
Captain, what's the situation?
Two jewels landed in the main hangar.
We follow them.
Just as Count Duke predicted.
Razodoroids.
Drop your weapon.
I say, throw it away.
OK.
- OK.
These are certainly Jedi fighters.
Did you press the button to stop?
- Not. And you?
There are more exits here.
We will not go out.
We want to get started.
R2, activate lift 31174.
Get in, R2.
- What that?
Do you hear, R2?
R2, activate lift 31174.
Back to work. Nothing that.
Activate lift 31174.
R2 ...
Always on the move.
R2, insert the microphone.
R2, can you hear me?
R2?
R2! R2!
Stop! Stop!
R2, we need to go up.
Hands up, thirsty.
R2, do you hear?
R2, can you hear me?
R2, we should go up, not downstairs.
Hey you!
Now its better.
Stupid little astrodroid.
Oh, you are.
My eyes! My eyes!
What was that?
- R2 is ...
No joke about wrinkled wires.
- Did I say something?
Stick to it.
- I did not say anything.
Chancellor.
- Are you ok?
Count Duke.
This time we'll be together.
- That's what I meant to say.
Go for help. You're not up to him.
He is Lord Sito.
Chancellor Palpatine,
Sito's masters are our specialty.
Your swords, please.
We do not want to make a mess
in front of the chancellor.
This time you will not get out, Duke.
I expected this.
My powers have doubled
since our meeting, Count.
Okay. Double ohol
double the fall.
Come on...
I feel a lot of fear in you, Skywalker.
There is hatred in you.
There is anger.
But you do not use them.
It's good, Anakin. Okay.
Kill him.
Kill him now.
I should not.
Kill him.
You did well, Anakin.
He was too dangerous
to live.
Yes, but he was
unarmed prisoner.
I was not supposed to do that.
Jedi do not work.
That is normal. He cut off your hand,
and you wanted to take revenge.
It was not your first time, Anakin.
Do you remember what you were telling me?
about your mother and sandstones?
Now we have to go,
before more droids come.
Anakin, no time.
We have to get off this ship
until it's too late.
Looks good.
- Leave him, or we will not get there.
His destiny will be the same as ours.
Get ready for the attack!
All batteries, burn! Fire away!
The elevator is not working.
R2, activate lift 3224.
Turn stabilizers.
- I'm turning the stabilizers.
On magnetis! On magnetis!
Auxiliary auxiliary engines.
Correct.
Slowly. We have a small problem.
Have I missed something?
- Hold on.
What is that?
- Yo.
R2. R2, a second lift.
Too late. Jump.
Let's see if we can in the hangar
we find something that can still fly.
R2, come here.
R2, can you hear me?
General, we found Jedi.
In the hall 328 are.
Activate shields.
Shields.
Wait. How did it happen?
We're smarter.
We do not seem to be.
I recommend the agreement.
- Stressing?
Yes. R2 will arrive
in a few moments ...
and then he will open
air shields.
You see? No problem.
Do not move.
Do you have a backup plan?
Oh yes.
Negotiator.
General Kenobi.
We were expecting you.
Sorry.
That was not some rescue.
- You're welcome.
I ...
Anakin Skywalker.
I expected someone to see you
to be a little ... older.
General Grievous.
You're lower than I expected.
The Jedi Swamp.
We have business, Anakin.
Try not to disturb him.
Your light swords will be
a nice addition to my collection.
This time she will not.
And this time you will not win.
R2.
Crush them!
Let them suffer.
Come on. Immediately!
Stay in your places!
Hold it.
Run away!
Hell with them.
Keep the ship in orbit.
- I understand.
You lost, General Kenobi.
Get out of here! Run away!
It's time to leave the ship.
All aircraft for departure
are launched.
Grievus.
Do you know how to manage this ship?
You think I'll let go of what's left?
- But?
Under these conditions, I would say it is
The ability to manage this is irrelevant.
Tie the belts.
Open all the covers.
Raise all the wings and stabilizers.
We lost something.
No worries.
We still have half a boat.
We really get on the speed.
Eight plus 60.
We're in the atmosphere.
- Hold it. Keep the horizontal.
Quiet.
Easy, R2.
5000.
Firefighters left and right.
We'll take you.
- I understand.
The runway is forward.
- We're overheated.
Another happy ground.
Are you coming, teach?
Not. I am not too brave for politics.
I have to file a report to the Chamber.
In addition, someone needs to show up.
Wait.
The whole operation was your idea.
Do not Forget, Anakin,
You saved me from the buzzer.
And you killed Count Duku,
and you saved the chancellor ...
carrying me out of the dark
on the back.
All thanks to your training.
Anakin, let's be honest.
Today you were a hero ...
and you deserve your day of glory
among politicians.
Okay. But you owe me a debt, and it does not
because I saved your skin for the tenth time.
Ninth time.
Keto Neimoidiom does not count.
We'll meet at the meeting.
Chancellor Palpatine,
Are you ok?
Yes. Thanking your two
Knight's Jedi.
They killed Count Duku,
but General Grievus escaped again.
General Grievus runs away and hides,
as always. It's a coward.
But since Count Duku is dead,
He's the leader of the Droid Army.
And I assure you ...
that the Senate will vote to continue the war
as long as Grievus is alive.
The larger Jedi will find Grievous
to put it first.
Watch it.
- Excuse me.
Come on, R2.
- The Republic has no words to thank you.
Thank you, Senator.
It can not be so bad.
In that I agree with you.
Actually, I need a service too.
But the fight is continued as long as the general
Grievous does not spare spare parts.
I will do everything I can in the Senate.
Sorry.
- Of course.
Oh, Anakin.
You missed me, Padme.
You whispered that you were killed.
I'm all right.
It seems like we were separated
whole eternity.
That could have happened
that the chancellor did not kidnap.
I think we would never return
from the siege of the Spherical Edge.
Wait. Not here.
- Yes, here.
I'm sitting all these fucking boots.
I do not care if they know we're married.
Anakin, do not say that.
Are you okay?
You're trembling.
What's happening?
Something wonderful happened.
Ani, I'm pregnant.
It is...
That's wonderful.
What can we do?
Now, we will not be concerned about anything.
Okay?
This is a happy moment.
The happiest moment in my life.
Yes, Lord Sidius?
General Grievuse ...
I suggest that the leaders of the separatists
transfer to Mustafar.
I'll do it, my lord.
The end of the war is approaching, General.
But the loss of Count Duku ...
His death is a necessary loss.
Soon I will have a new student ...
much younger
and much more powerful.
Ani, I want our baby to be born
at home, at Nabu.
We can go to the lakes,
where no one will know ...
where we can be sure.
I can go earlier
and fix a baby room.
I know the perfect place.
Right next to the gardens.
You are so Beautiful.
It's just that
that I am so loved.
No, that's because I am
so much for love with you.
So, Love made you blind?
I did not mean that much.
But it's probably true.
Anakin, help me!
What's bothering you?
Nothing.
I remember when I gave you this.
How long will it take to become
Sincere to each other?
I dreamed something.
- Bad?
Like what I dreamed of
about the mother, just before she died.
And?
I dreamed of you.
Excuse me.
It was just a dream.
You're dying at birth.
A baby?
I do not know.
It was just a dream.
- I will not let this dream come true.
Baby will change our life.
I doubt that the Queen will let me
Yes, and I'll be in the Senate.
If the Chamber finds out that you are your father,
will throw you out ...
I know.
Do you think Obi-Van?
could he help us?
We do not need his help.
Our baby is a blessing.
Suspicion?
Awareness.
These visions ...
These are visions of pain, suffering.
Death.
You talk about yourself
or about someone you know?
About someone.
Close to you?
Yes.
You have to be careful
when you are experiencing the future, Anakin.
Fear of loss is the path
to the dark side.
I will not let you
These visions are realized, teach Yude.
Death is a natural part of life.
Rejoice over those around you
which is transformed into the Force.
Do not complain.
Let them not reach you.
Privileges are led by jealousy.
It's the shadow of greed.
What should I do, teach me Yoda?
Learn not to tie ...
for all that you are afraid to lose.
You missed the report
about the siege of the Knife Edge.
Excuse me. I kept it.
I have no excuse.
- In short, it takes place very well.
Saleukami fell, and teach him Vos
he transferred the troops to Boz Piti.
What's wrong then?
The Senate is expected to deliver today
more executive power for the chancellor.
It just means less notice
and more action. Is that bad?
It will make it easier for us
to end this war.
Beware of your friend Palpatine.
What can I keep?
He was looking for your presence.
- Why?
He did not want to say.
Did not he inform the Council?
That's unusual, is not it?
All this is unusual.
And that's what worries me.
I hope you trust me, Anakin.
Of course.
I need your help, son.
What do you mean?
I count on you.
For what? I do not understand.
To be your eyes, your ears
and the voice of the Republic.
I name you for my personal
representatives in the Jedi Council.
Me?
Teacher?
I'm happy, sir.
But the Chamber only elects its members.
They will not accept this.
I think they will.
You need them.
More than you think.
This appointment of the Council
will not be easy to approve.
This move cares
Chancellor Palpatine.
I understand.
You are in the Council,
but we do not give you
Rank is taught.
What?
How can you do it?
This is unheard of.
It's unlawful.
How can you be in the Council
not to learn?
Sit down, young Skywalker.
Excuse me, teach me.
We searched
all systems in the Republic ...
but we did not find a trace
General Grievous.
Grievous is hiding in the Communication edge.
You need to search for remote systems.
We can not separate a lot of ships.
What about the droid attack
on Vukije?
It's necessary to go right there
We are sending a group of attackers.
He is right. That system
we must not lose.
I'll go.
I'm in good relations with the Wookiees.
Then it's solved.
Joda will take the clone of clones
as reinforcement of the Vukijim on Kašik.
Let the Power be with all of us.
What's that nonsense?
Prime me to the Council
but they do not give me the title of the teacher.
That's in the history of Jedi
it never happened. It's an insult.
Calm down, Anakin.
It's a great honor.
Being in the Council at your age ...
it never happened before.
It's about
that you are too close to the chancellor.
The Chamber does not like it when it blends
in the affairs of the Jedi.
I swear to you,
I did not ask to be in the Council.
Did you want that?
Your friendship with the Chancellor
Palpatine seems to have paid off.
It has nothing to do with this.
The only reason the Chamber approved it
your appointment,
is that the Chancellor believes you.
And?
Anakin, on your side.
I did not want to get you into this situation.
What situation?
The Chamber wants you to report it
about all the actions of the chancellor.
They want to know what he's up to.
Want to follow the chancellor?
But it's a betrayal.
- It's a war, Anakin.
Why did not the Chamber give me this task?
while we were at the meeting?
This task must not be public.
The chancellor is not a bad man, Obi-Vane.
He talked to me. Watch out for me
Since I came here.
That's why you have to help us.
Anakin, we are dedicated to the Senate,
not his leader ...
who managed to remain in position
long after the expiration of the mandate.
The Senate demanded
to stay longer.
Yes, but he uses his feelings, Anakin.
Something is not right.
You're asking me to do something
which contradicts the codex of Jedi.
Against the Republic.
Against mentors and friends.
That's not right.
Why are you asking me?
The Chamber seeks.
Anakin did not accept his new task
with lots of excitement.
It's very dangerous
merge them two.
I do not think Anakin does
can with this end come to an end.
I have no confidence in him.
With due respect, learn,
Is not he the one chosen?
Should not he destroy Site
and to bring balance to the Force?
So it says the prophecy.
A prophecy that maybe
misinterpreted.
He will not let me down.
He never let me down.
I hope you're right.
Sometimes I wonder what's going on
with a row of jewels.
I think this war is destroying
principles of the Republic.
Have you ever thought
that we may be on the wrong side?
What do you mean?
What if the democracy we served
no longer exists,
and the Republic has become just that evil
for whose destruction we are fighting?
I do not believe.
And you sound like a separatist.
This war means
less hearing.
You are now closer to the Chancellor
than anybody.
Please, ask him to stop the fighting
and allow diplomacy to continue.
Do not ask me to do it.
Submit a proposal to the Senate,
where such a request belongs.
What is it?
- Nothing.
Do not do it. Do not get me wrong.
Let me help you.
Hug me.
Like you hugged me
next to the lake on Nabu.
So long ago, when it did not exist
nothing but our Love.
No politics, no conspiracy, no war.
You wanted me to come, Chancellor.
- Yes, Anakin.
Come closer. I have good news.
Our units
clones of intelligence ...
they discovered
where General Grievus is.
It is hiding in Utapau.
Finally.
We can catch that monster
and to end this war.
I would be worried about wisdom
of the entire Council ...
not to choose you for this task.
You are by far the best choice.
Have a seat.
Leave us.
You know I can not rely on it
to the Jedi Council.
If they have not already gotten you
In his plot, he will soon.
I'm not sure I understand.
You must feel what I feel.
More Jedi
wants to control the Republic.
They're planning to betray me.
I do not think so...
- Anakin.
Examine your feelings.
You know that, do not you?
I know they do not believe you.
Not the Senate.
Not the Republic.
Not democracy, if we do.
I have to admit that it is my trust
in them.
Why?
They asked you to do something
What looks unfair to you, is not it?
They asked me to follow me, did not I?
I do not...
I do not know what to say.
Remember
what you learned at the beginning.
All who are able to gain power
They are afraid that they will not lose.
Even Jedi.
- The Jedi use their power for good.
Good depends
from the point of view, Anakin.
City and Jedi
are almost everything similar ...
including the desire
for more power.
The cities draw strength from their passion.
They think inward -
just for yourself.
And not the Jedi?
Jedi are unselfish.
They care only about others.
Have you ever heard of a tragedy?
Darta Plaguesa Wise?
And I thought you were not. That story
Jedi would not tell you.
It's the legend of the Sita.
Dart Plagues was
Dark Lord of the Seas ...
so powerful and wise ...
that he could use Silu
to affect the midichlorans ...
to create ... life.
So he knew the dark side ...
that even those he likes could have
to save ...
from death.
He could really have saved her
People from death?
Dark side of the Force
the way to many abilities ...
which some consider unnatural.
What happened to him?
He became so powerful ...
that he was the only one to fear ...
was a loss of power.
Which, of course, eventually happened.
Unfortunately, he taught his student
everything he knew.
Then the student killed him at bedtime.
Irony.
He could save others from death ...
And not yourself.
Is it possible to get such a power?
Not from Jedi.
All the Red units here!
Palpatine thinks General Grievus is
on Utapau?
They intercepted part of the message ...
in diplomatic mail
from President Utapau.
We have to do something.
Capturing General Grievous
will end this war.
Quickly and decisively
We have to work.
The chancellor asked ...
to lead a march.
The Chamber will only decide
who will go ...
not a chancellor.
It is necessary to study,
someone more experienced.
I agree.
Teach Kenobi to go.
Yes.
Okay. The meeting is over.
Drugs were launched
main generators.
Now is the time, Commander.
- Yes sir.
You're hurting!
U zaklon!
I'll need you for this.
- I agree.
However, it can be shown
that we are on the wrong track.
Learn.
I disappointed you. I'm not comfortable
appreciated your learning.
I was a kid
And I apologize.
But I am so unhappy with the Council.
You are strong and wise, Anakin,
and I'm proud of you.
I train you out of the way.
I've taught you everything I know.
And you became a lot of Jedi Jedi
than I'll ever be.
But be patient, Anakin.
The Chamber will soon give you
called by the teacher.
Obi-Vane,
let the Power come with you.
Good-bye, old friend.
Let the Power come with you.
Fortunately, most cities are concentrated
on this small continent.
On the other hand.
I'll draw their attention
until you arrive.
Just do not stay long.
- Well, did I ever let you down?
Okay. It's not for me to destroy it
All droids until you arrive.
Save energy.
Can not.
Do not give up, Padme.
Obi-Van was here, was not he?
He dropped this morning.
What did he want?
Take care of you.
He says you're under a lot of pressure.
I feel lost.
Lost? What do you mean?
Obi-Van and the Chamber do not believe me.
They trust you with all your heart.
Something is happening.
I'm not a jaddy like I should be.
I want more.
And I know I should not.
You demand too much from yourself.
I've found a way to save you.
- To save me?
Out of my basketball.
Does that bother you?
I do not want to lose you, Padme.
I will not die at birth, Ani.
I assure you.
- No, I assure you.
Hello, young Jedi.
What brings you
to our remote haven?
Unfortunately, war.
There is no war here ...
unless you bring it with you.
If you let me, I need fuel ...
and your city for the base while I'm looking for the general
Grievous in nearby systems.
Here is.
It keeps us hostage.
They're watching us.
- I understand.
Tenth level,
hi droids of combat droids.
Tell your people to go to the shelter.
If you have warriors, now is the time.
Take a boatman.
Tell the Cody that I've made contact.
Does he bring more warriors?
- He did not say.
Army of the Republic, fast
they will find us here.
I'm sending you to the Mustafar system
on the Communication edge.
It's a planet of volcanic origin.
There you will be sure.
- Safe?
Chancellor Palpatine managed to
Move to your distress, General.
No Count Duku, I doubt
that you can protect us.
Be grateful, vicekraLju,
you did not find me in the hand.
Your ship is waiting.
Hello.
General Kenobi.
You're very brave.
Kill him.
Back.
I'll deal with this myself
I'm garbage from the jade.
You're on the move.
You fool.
Count Duku taught me
Your Jedi skills.
In the attack, Kenobi.
Had an army or not ...
you surely realize you're done.
I would not say.
Cover that corner.
LearnLu Vindu, can I interrupt you?
General Kenobi came into contact
with General Grievous ...
and we started the attack.
Thank you, commander.
Anakin, bring it to the chancellor
this report.
His reaction will show us
what's going on.
Yes, teach me.
I feel conspiracy to destroy the Jedi.
The Dark Side of the Force
surrounds the chancellor.
If after the destruction of Grievous
does not give up ...
authorities...
then we need to get him out of position.
The larger the Jedi must
take control of the Senate ...
to ensure a quiet transition.
If this is how we think of darkness
will take us under his own.
We have to be very careful.
Chancellor.
We just received a report
from the teacher Kenobi.
He broke up with General Grievous.
Let's just hope it is
Learn Kenobi to come up with a challenge.
I should be there with him.
It bothers me
what I see is the Chamber ...
Does not appreciate your gift
completely.
You're not wondering why
Will not they call you teacher?
I would like to know.
I feel more and more ...
to excuse me from the Council.
I know there's something there
they do not tell me about Sila.
They do not believe you, Anakin.
See your future.
They know your power will be too strong
to control it.
You have to break through a network of lies
which the Jedi splintered around you.
Let me help you learn
fine Force.
How do you know all this about the Force?
My mentor taught me
all about the Force.
Even the nature of the dark side.
Do you know the dark side?
To understand this great secret ...
you should study all of her sides ...
not just dogmatic
narrow vision of the Jedi.
If you want to become
a complete and wise leader ...
you have to take a wider view of Sil.
Beware of Jedi, Anakin.
Only with me can you reach
greater power than any jade.
Learn the dark side of the Force ...
and you can save your wife ...
from certain death.
What did you say?
Use my knowledge. Please.
You are the Master of Sita.
I know what's bothering you.
Listen to me.
Do not even be a pawn
Greater Jedi.
Since when I know you,
looking for life,
bigger than the life of ordinary jewels.
Life with meaning,
with conscience.
Will you kill me?
- Of course I would.
I know you would.
I feel your anger.
Concentrates you ...
makes you stronger.
I'll teach you
More Jedi.
Of course. You should.
But you're not sure
what are their intentions, right?
I'll be quick to discover the truth
in all this.
You have great wisdom, Anakin.
Know the power of the dark side.
Power to save Padma.
So uncivilized.
LearnLu Vindu,
I need to talk to you.
Skywalker, we just got news
that Obi-Van killed General Grievous.
Let's take care of ...
to return the chancellor
powers to the Senate.
He will not leave power.
I just learned the terrible truth.
I think Chancellor Palpatine,
Lord of the Seas.
Lord Sita?
Yes. The one we're looking for.
How do you know that?
- He knows Silu.
He learned to use it
dark side.
Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
Then our greatest fear came true.
We need to work fast,
that the order of Jedi will survive.
Teach me, Chancellor
It's very powerful.
You'll need my help
if you want to catch him.
For your own good,
Do not get involved in this.
I feel a lot of bother in you,
young Skywalker.
There is a lot of fear
which blurs your judgment.
I have to go, teach me.
- Not.
If it is that you told me the truth,
you'll get my confidence.
But for now, stay here.
Wait in the chambers of the Chamber
until we get back.
Yes, teach me.
You know, do not you ...
that if the Jedi destroy me ...
all chances to save her
to be lost.
LearnLu Vindu. I suppose it is
General Grievus is destroyed.
I have to say you came
sooner than I expected you.
In the name of the galactic Senate of the Republic ...
You're under arrest, Chancellor.
Are you threatening me,
teach me Jedi?
The Senate will decide on your destiny.
I am the Senate.
- Not yet.
Then this is a betrayal.
You're under arrest, my lord.
Anakin, I told you he would come
to this. I was right.
The Jedi take power.
Tyranny Sita never
he will not come back.
You lost.
You will die!
He's a traitor!
I have the power to save
the one you love.
You have to choose.
Do not listen to him, Anakin!
Do not let him kill me.
I can not stand it for a long time.
Can not. I'm bad.
I'm too weak.
Anakin!
Help me. Help me!
I can not anymore.
I'll finish this once and for all.
You can not.
He must be tried.
He controls the Senate and the courts.
It's too dangerous
to stay alive.
I'm too weak.
Do not kill me. Please.
- Jedi do not act like that.
He must remain alive.
Please do not.
- I need.
Please do not!
Power!
Unlimited power!
What did I do?
You fulfill your destiny, Anakin.
Be my student.
Learn to use
dark side of the Force.
I'll do whatever you're looking for.
Okay.
Just help me
I save Padmin's life.
I can not live without it.
Only one man has gained power
to avoid death ...
but if we cooperate ...
I know we can discover that secret.
I give up...
your learning.
Okay.
The power is strong in you.
You will become a powerful Sit.
From now on your name is ...
Dart ... Wade.
Thank you, teach me.
Get up.
Since the Chamber did not believe you,
My young student ...
I think you're the only Jedi
who does not know about this conspiracy.
When the Jedi know
What happened here ...
it will kill us and all senators.
I agree.
The next move is the Chamber
it will be against the Senate.
Every Jedi ...
including your friend
Obi-Van Kenobi ...
it is now an unpleasant Republic.
I understand, my lord.
We have to work fast.
Jedi are unbearable.
If we do not destroy them all,
Civil war will not end.
First, I want you to go to the Temple of Jedi.
We'll get them unprepared.
Do what you have, Lord Wade.
Do not hesitate.
Do not have mercy.
It's only then that the dark side will
You will be quite strong ...
to rescue Padma.
And what about the other Jedi
in the whole galaxy?
With their betrayal
we will calculate.
When you kill all the Jedi in the temple ...
go to the Mustafar system.
Liquidate vice-squad Gunra ...
and all the others
leaders of separatists.
The City will do it again
rule the galaxy!
I ...
We'll have ... peace.
Sergeant, over here!
Quickly! All!
All Red units, let's go!
Come on. Here we go!
Commander, contact
their troops.
Tell them to move to a higher level.
All right Sir.
Along the way,
I think this is what you need.
Thank you, Kodi. Here we go.
We need to get a fight.
I understand.
Komandante Kodi ...
time is.
Execute order 66.
Yes, my lord.
Blow it out!
Come on!
Execute order 66.
It will be done, Master.
LearnLu Skywalker,
There are too many of them.
What can we do?
Kancelera office reports
Lord Anakin returned to the Temple of Jedi.
Do not worry.
I'm sure it will be fine.
What's going on here?
- The uprising is up.
Do not worry.
The situation is under control.
Excuse me, sir.
Time to go.
Yes.
Kill him!
Do not worry about him.
Let him go.
All Vukies are dead.
Go east.
Yes sir.
Goodbye, Tarfule.
Goodbye, Chubaka.
I will miss you.
I hope we can intercept
a few Jedi ...
before you get out
in this disaster.
Did you find Kenobi?
Sir, nobody could
to survive this fall.
Start putting people on ships.
Come on.
Emergency code 913.
I have no contact
not on one frequency.
LearnLyu Kenobi.
I repeat.
Learn from Kenobi.
Senator Organa. My army of clones
she turned against me. I need help.
We just saved
Learn Yoda.
Looks like this is an ambush
everywhere.
We are sending you our coordinates.
Not so loud.
Are you okay? I heard they were attacking
the temple of Jedi.
Smoke is seen here.
- I'm all right.
I came to see
Are you and the baby safe?
What happens?
The jews tried to
make a revolt in the Republic.
I can not believe.
I personally saw that she was learning Le Vindu
tried to kill the chancellor.
What are you going to do?
I will not betray the Republic.
I am loyal to the chancellor ...
Senate
you too.
And Obi-Vanu?
- I do not know.
Many Jedi were killed.
Let's just hope
that he remained loyal to the chancellor.
Anakin, I'm scared.
Have faith, Love.
Soon everything will get settled.
The chancellor trusted me
a very important mission.
Separatists gathered
in the Mustafar system.
I'm going there to end this war.
Wait for me to come back.
Everything will be different.
I promise.
Please, wait for me.
Under great stress, R2.
Take care, my little friend.
Oh, ma'am,
Can I help you somehow?
No, thank you, 3PO.
I feel so helpless.
How many Jedi survived?
None of us answered.
I saw that they were soldiers
attacked the temple of Jedi.
So I went to search for Iodine.
Do we have any connection with the temple?
We got an encrypted message
about withdrawal.
He wants all Jedi to return to the temple.
He says the war is over.
- Then we gotta get back.
If it has a backlog,
he will be trapped and killed.
You suggest encrypting the signal
remove?
Yes, teach me.
Too much is on the cube.
I agree.
A little more knowledge
it can light our way.
The plan is taking place
as you said, master.
You worked well, Vicki.
When my new student
Dart Wade arrives ...
will take care of you.
There's a message from the Chancellor
Office, sir.
Let her go.
- Yes sir.
Senator Organa, Supreme Chancellor
Requires your presence ...
at a special session of the Congress.
I will come.
- They'll expect you.
Maybe it's a trap.
- I do not think so.
The chancellor will not be able to control it
hiLjade star systems ...
not to leave the Senate untouched.
If there is
special session of the Congress ...
it will be easier for us to
we enter the temple of Jedi.
R2, stay with the boat.
Welcome, Lord Wade.
We were expecting you.
And the rebellion of Jedi is shaken.
What happened?
The chancellor talks about the Jedi plot
to make an uprising in the Senate.
We will catch the rest of the jar
and to defeat.
Not even children survived.
They were not killed by clones.
He was killed by a light sword.
Who?
Who could do that?
Assassination not me ...
He broke me and left me scum.
But, I assure you.
I've never been more determined!
Stop!
To guarantee security
and lasting stability ...
The Republic will be reorganized ...
in the first Galactic Empire!
For a safe and stable society.
So here's how freedom dies.
With a thunderous applause.
The war is over.
Lord Sidius promised us peace.
We just want to ...
I corrected the code to warn you
all the remaining Jedi do not come.
Yes clones ...
discover that update
it will take a long time.
Wait. Learn.
I need to know something.
If you are looking at security footage,
you will only find yourself suffering.
I need to know the truth, teach me.
Not possible.
You were good,
new pupil.
Now, Lord Wade ...
go and bring peace to Empire.
I can not watch.
We have to destroy Site.
Send me to kill the Emperor.
I will not kill Anakin.
You're not too strong
to fight Lord Sidius.
He's like my brother.
I can not do it.
It's a Young Skywalker
distorted the dark side.
The young man you were training
no longer exists.
It was destroyed by Dart Wade.
I do not know where he is
Emperor sent.
I do not know where to look.
Use your feelings, Obi-Wane,
and you will find him.
When was the last time you saw him?
Yesterday.
- And do you know where it is now?
Padme, I need your help.
He's in great danger.
- From the Sita?
From myself.
Anakin crossed the dark side.
You're wrong.
How can you say that?
I've seen a security hologram ...
how he ...
kills children.
Not Anakin. He could not.
He was deceived by a lie.
She's all deceived us.
It looks like the chancellor behind all this,
including war.
Palpatine is the master of the Sita
which we are looking for.
After the death of Duke Duke,
Anakin became his new disciple.
I do not believe you.
Can not.
I have to find him.
You will kill him, will not you?
Has become
very dangerous.
Can not.
Anakin is a father, is not he?
I'm very sorry.
Ma'am, let me go with you.
- No danger.
The fighting has stopped.
And this is personal nature.
How do you want, ma'am,
but I do not agree at all.
It'll be fine, Captain.
This is something I have to do myself.
In addition, 3PO will look after me.
Oh my God.
You know what? Flying is becoming clear to me.
I took care of the separatists,
Learn.
Then it's over.
You restored peace
and justice to the galaxy.
Send a message
ships of the Trade Federation.
All units of droids
they must be immediately exploded.
All right, Master.
I saw your ship.
What are you doing here?
- I was worried about you.
Obi-Wan told me something terrible.
What?
He said you crossed
on the dark side.
If you ... killed kids.
Obi-Van is trying to get you
turned against me.
He care about us.
Our?
He knows.
He wants to help you.
Anakin, I only want your Love.
Love will not save you, Padme.
Only my new powers can do it.
- At what price?
You are good.
Do not do it.
I will not lose you
as I lost my mother.
I am becoming more powerful than I am
any Jedi could dream.
And I'm doing it for you.
To protect you.
Come with me.
Help me raise our kid.
Let's leave it all
while we still can.
Do not you understand?
We no longer have to run.
I brought peace to the Republic.
I'm more powerful than the chancellor.
I can take it off.
And you and I can together
to rule the galaxy ...
and we're trying to be the same
how we want.
I do not believe what I hear.
Obi-Van was right.
You changed.
I do not want to listen anymore
about Obi-Vanu.
That jeray turned against me.
If you did not turn against me.
I do not know you anymore.
You're breaking my heart.
You're going through the road
which I can not go.
Because of Obi-Vana?
Because of what you did.
What are you going to do?
Stop it. Stop it now. Come back.
I love you.
- LažLjivice!
You're on his side!
You brought him here to kill me.
Let her go, Anakin.
Let her go.
You turned it against me!
You did it yourself.
You will not take it from me!
Your anger and the need for power
have already done so.
You let the dark lord do you
Turn around ...
until you become exactly what you are
what you swore to destroy.
Do not hold on to me, Obi-Vane.
I missed it
all the lies of Jedi.
I'm not afraid of the dark side,
as you.
I brought peace ...
freedom, justice and security
his empire.
Your empire?
Do not make me kill you.
Anakin, I'm devoted
Republic, democracy!
If you're not with me ...
then you are unpleasant.
Only one Sit is so exciting.
I'll do what I have to do.
You will try.
I hear you have a new one
pupils, imperators.
Or to call you
Dart Sidius?
Learn Yoda.
You are alive.
Surprised?
Your ancestry blinds you,
Learn Lord Joda.
Now you will experience ...
all power of the dark side.
I'm waiting for a moment ...
Little My Green Friend.
The jealousy is no longer at all.
It will not be so,
if I'm wondering.
Your reign is over.
And it was not too short.
If you are so powerful ...
Why are you leaving?
You will not stop me.
Dart Wade will become more powerful
from both of them.
Your faith in the new student
it can be wrong.
Like your faith in the dark side.
Hurry up. We'll have to
Careful to set.
Activate radio-far
when you're ready.
There is no sign
to his body, sir.
Then he's not dead.
- Duplicate the search.
I understand. Immediately, sir.
Tell Captain Kagi to give me right away
Prepare a craft.
Yes, my lord.
- I feel Lord Wade is in danger.
I have to go to exile.
I failed.
I let you down, Anakin.
I failed you.
I should have known that Jedi
they are plotting to take power.
Anakin, Chancellor Palpatine is evil!
From my point of view, the Jedi are evil.
Then you are lost!
This is your end, teach me.
It's over, Anakin.
I'm at a height.
You underestimate my power.
Do not test her.
You were the one chosen!
It was predicted that you would destroy
Site, not you will join them!
To bring balance into the Force,
not letting her leave it in the dark!
I hate you!
You were my brother, Anakin.
I loved you.
LearnLyu Kenobi.
Ms. Padme is on board.
Yes. Please hurry.
We have to leave this horrible place.
Is Anakin okay?
Here, Your Majesty.
Here it is.
He's still alive.
Immediately bring a medical capsule.
I understand. Immediately.
Excuse me, study Yude.
Obi-Van Kenobi contacted us.
We'll take her to the health center.
Quickly.
Medical view
It's completely healthy.
We're losing it for inexplicable reasons.
Dies?
- We do not know why.
She lost the fruit to live.
We have to quickly operate it,
to save the babies.
Baby?
Wears twins.
Onion.
Oh, Luke.
Girl.
- Leila.
He has goodness in him.
I know that.
I know that ... more ...
Lord Wade.
Can you hear me?
Yes, teach me.
Where's Padme?
Is she safe?
Is it good?
Looks like you killed her in your anger.
Me? Not possible.
She was alive. I felt!
Not!
Hidden and out of danger
Children must be.
We have to take them somewhere where Sit
they will not feel their presence.
We need to split them.
My wife and I will take the girl.
We always thought
to adopt a girl.
It will be driven with us.
A boy?
On Tatuin.
Send it to his family.
I'll take the kid
and I'll take care of him.
We will disappear until it is
the right time.
Learn Lee Kenobi, wait.
In your solitude on Tatuin,
I have training for you.
Training?
The old friend found him
the path to immortality.
Someone who's back
from the lower world of the Force.
Your former teacher.
Kui-Gon?
I'll teach you how to
You communicate with him.
Captain Antiles.
- Yes, Your Honor?
I'm giving you these droids.
Treat them nicely.
Clean them.
Delete the memory
protocol droid.
What?
Oh no!